This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy has returned to Marineford with Rayleigh and Jinbei at his side.
For what reason did they go back?
And why did Luffy ring the Oxbell?
With hopes it will reach my friends!
Big news spreading fast!
On a certain island along the Grand Line...
Times have been rough since you got locked up.
We couldn't even sleep at night, but we knew we had to get you back somehow.
We sailed all over in search of you, surviving countless hardships along the way.
But then...
We saw our very own Captain, a hero in the newspaper!
Welcome back!
Finally!
We're with you till the end.
A little wait like that is nothing.
Our very own Captain Buggy leading us into the New World!
I didn't know you guys cared about me so much!
I missed all of you too!
Captain!
Bunch of liars.
I seem to recall you giving up on him.
Welcome to the crew, fellas!
I'm the first mate of the Buggy Pirates, Beast Tamer Moji!
Brother Moji!
And I'm the Chief of Staff, Kabaji!
Brother Kabaji!
And this here's my buddy!
The one and only Richie!
Richie!
Impressive.
Looks like what the paper said about your new followers turned out to be true.
Though I'm almost afraid to ask how you got so many infamous criminals to follow you.
Give me some credit.
Clearly when it comes to scoundrels, I'm a natural born leader.
Oh, by the way, I picked up a little something on my trip that you might find interesting.
Huh?
Ta-da!
It can't be!
Very nice!
You finally found Captain John's armband, huh?
Sure did!
Don't leave me in suspense!
How did you get your hands on this?
That idiot's straw hat gave it to me without a second thought!
Everything's coming up, Flashy! The wind is blowing my way!
Could it be Buggy was meant to be king of the pirates?
Oh, speaking of straw hat, he's still making a name for himself after the war.
Huh?
You didn't know?
He caused quite a stir returning to Marineford.
You're kidding me!
He was barely alive when I last saw him.
And now this?
Uh, let's see.
First son of the sea, Jinbei, teams up with straw hat.
Dark King Rayleigh joins them.
Rayleigh?
Ah!
This is a joke, right?
Since when did Rayleigh get involved with straw hats?
This just keeps on getting messier.
I can't wrap my head around this at all!
Wait a sec.
If I'm remembering it correctly,
Straw Hat's pop is the revolutionary dragon.
On top of that, his grandpa's garb.
It could only mean one thing.
Really, must be Straw Hat's long-lost uncle!
Hey, Buggy!
A carrier bat brought a message for you from the government.
How did they find me?
Did someone rat me out?
The Navy must be trying to strike me down before I'm too strong!
Which means the message is my final warning.
Hey!
Give me that letter!
It can't be!
This is simply unbelievable!
Hey, that's from me!
Stop it!
Meanwhile, at the Saba Odi Archipelago, along the Grand Line,
the Thousand Sunny waits for its crew,
anchored at Grove Number 44.
Either you hand over the ship, or we bust your faces in!
You can't fool us!
We know it belongs to Straw Hat, and we know he's Dragon's son!
The Navy's bound to pay good money for it,
so walk away and we won't hurt ya!
Since you and I are in the same line of work,
give it up now and you'll get a cut of the profit!
Easy, right?
How about it, Flying Fish Riders?
Hmm.
What? I'm handsome?
I didn't say that, weirdo!
We're true, it's played around!
You punks ain't getting nothing from me!
Ugh!
Enough of this!
Huh?
Listen up, you losers!
I, the very handsome Duval, refuse to let a bunch of ugly fools like you become popular!
Uh, I mean, try to steal our friend's ship on my watch!
Stay unpopular!
Well, as long as he protects the ship, we're okay!
You won't touch this ship as long as I live, and before I die, I'm gonna touch a girl!
I mean, if you touch it, you're gonna die!
The ship, I mean, not the girl!
The bottom line is, you're not getting near the Sunny,
but if you want to fight, come and get it!
Yeah, tough guy!
Come on! Let's book it!
Wow, Duval! Nice one!
The girls won't leave me alone because I'm so handsome!
Thanks for the support! I love you two!
The Mermaid Cafe should obviously be the first stop, don't you think?
It's so in style!
Nah, once they get back, I'm sure the first place they'll want to see is the Fishman Karate Training Hall!
Wait a minute! I already promised Brooke I'd introduce him to the Mermaid Princess!
Hey, boss! It's like she doesn't even know you're there!
I can wait! That's cool!
Oh, I almost forgot to ask! The Straw Hats can use their Vivre cards to get back here, right?
Now that we all know Luffy Toon's alive, they should be here soon!
Maybe. If they're far away, it might take them a while, but Ray found Monkey easy enough with his Vivre card.
Until then, we have to protect this ship.
Don't you worry, because we're here to do exactly that!
Whether it's the Navy or somebody else, nobody's gonna take the ship!
So far, you're doing great!
Hey, Duvall! We've got a huge problem! Kuma's heading this way!
Kuma? Do I know a Kuma?
Oh, right!
It's the Warlord! Bartholomew Kuma!
Hey, Kuma!
Relax, everyone.
That man, he came to speak with Ray before.
So tell me, Kuma, whose side are you on?
Meanwhile, on Sandy Island, part of Alabasta Kingdom on the Grand Line,
the capital city, Alubarna.
What happened to the pirates?
We chased them away. The city is virtually undamaged.
I see. Good job.
We're strengthening security across the country.
Ever since Whitebeard's death, pirates around the world are more active.
Our region is no exception.
We have to be careful for the time being.
If only all pirates were like Straw Hat Luffy and his crew.
But such is not the case.
Speaking of Luffy, have you read today's newspaper?
Yes, I did.
Whoa!
Vivi was ecstatic when she read about Luffy and the others!
Huh. Of course she was.
But...
Karu!
Take a look at this!
Thank goodness! Luffy is still alive!
I'm so glad. I just knew he'd be okay.
Huh? What?
Within a single moment, her entire demeanor changed and all of her joy suddenly vanished.
She took the newspaper and ran towards her room.
Huh. What's that on Luffy's arm?
Numbers? Is it a code?
Well, it's not a tattoo, right?
That doesn't really seem like Luffy's style, does it?
Meanwhile, in another city, in another country, along the Grand Line...
Whoa! Hey! What's a hardcore pirate like him doing on our island?
Hush! He can hear you!
It's only been three weeks since the war.
They were lucky to escape death at Marineford.
What the hell would bring them back there?
Straw Hat's probably cooking up some plan.
Either that or he's just crazy.
That sounds about right.
He was badly injured in the fight, though.
Takes someone pretty special to get back on their feet so quickly.
You saying I'm slower than Straw Hat?
Trying to challenge your old boss?
I'm done resting, don't worry.
There's no point in staying here any longer.
It's time to set out for the new world.
Are you coming, Daz?
Of course I am.
The news of Luffy's latest exploits, as well as his return to World War II.
The news of Luffy's latest exploits, as well as his return to Marineford, quickly spread to each crew member's home.
The news of Luffy's latest exploits, as well as his return to Marineford, quickly spread to each crew member's hometown.
The news of Luffy's latest exploits, as well as Luffy's latest exploits, as well as his return to Marineford, quickly spread to each crew member's hometown.
Get a load of this, Ace!
You saved your little brother's life! Luffy is alive!
Rest in peace, you brat!
Meanwhile, on the Grand Line...
Really sorry you had to go so far out of your way.
It's nothing. We're pretty used to being away from home.
Um, what are you doing?
Huh? We're making sure that you're resting properly, of course!
Orders from the Snake Princess herself!
But she couldn't stay, because she collapsed from a severe case of heart cluttering.
So here we are, keeping a close eye on you.
I hope they get the message, wherever they are.
They'll understand if they see the article. Obviously, this isn't something you would do on a whim.
Would you stop, please?
That said, your swordsman can be a bit daft. Still, I think you'll figure it out somehow. They are your crew, after all. If anyone can understand you, it's them.
Above the Grand Line, high in the air...
I got it, Luffy! Don't worry! I'm changing plans, Dad! Yeah! Okay! Okay!
On the giant bridge, reaching across the East Blue...
So that's it. Very well, then.
Something in the paper again? Good news, I hope.
Interesting as always, Luffy.
And in Kamabaka Kingdom...
Roger that, Captain.
What's going on?
The Bowen Islands.
I gotta find a way off! I gotta find a way off this island!
Ouch! Ouch! I'm so sick of this!
Get away from me! I don't care what you have to say!
One way or another, I'm gonna get to Luffy even if it kills me!
Look at that! I think I made it! Is that the shore?!
You've barely gone 50 feet.
No!
Damn it! Why does everything here have to be so delicious?!
I'm still hungry!
Stop it, Usoppin! You're already dangerously obese-y!
Don't give in to the island's trap!
Can't you see I'm busy?!
Huh? Huh?
I've got it!
What is it this time, Usoppin?
Yes, Luffy! Yes!
The Sky Island with area.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, young lady!
Where are you running off to?
Not now!
Well, I thought you should know that they closed the balloon terminal after you tried to escape!
And since the island's so small, there's nowhere to run!
Well, you better come up with something quick then! I have to get away from here!
I know I'm your hostage!
But why don't we go back to my place for a while?
Huh?
Uh...
Hey, hey! Why don't we go inside already?
Now that is interesting!
But honestly, Luffy, how about how I feel, huh? You're so selfish!
Better hurry, young lady! They're coming this way!
Future Land, Baltimore.
Hey, Grandpa, think something bad happened to Mr. Frank?
I'm sorry, kitten. It's too late now. Just forget the whole incident. You'll be better off.
That explosion was massive. There's no way he's still alive.
And I told him not to press that self-destruct button repeatedly.
Ah!
One, two, three.
Oh! That was a doozy!
Ah! You're alive!
Ah!
Huh. Uh-huh.
I got you, boss.
Ah!
The Tanagana Kingdom.
Woo-hoo!
I don't have time to dawdle around while my friends are still out there.
Hey!
Huh?
Are you done eating yet? Let me have those plates.
Oh, go ahead. Also, I think I asked you gentlemen for the newspaper. There might be a follow-up story about my friend that I'd like to read.
Surely you understand.
Real funny. You don't even have eyes in that empty head of yours. How the hell are you supposed to read?
I may joke about my appearance, but it's hurtful when someone else does it.
Too bad, Freak Show. You're up soon, so get ready. Here.
It's Luffy!
Greetings! Feast your eyes, ladies and gentlemen, on these magnificent living bones!
Woo-hoo!
Ah, how very clever of you.
No need to worry, Luffy. I understand.
The ruins of Moggy Kingdom.
You gonna sleep there forever? Would you get up? Quit trying to leave!
Do you like getting stomped by a bunch of baboons? Look at it from my side! I've gotta take care of you!
Leave me alone, will ya?
Very well. I guess you don't need this. I brought today's newspaper from the news coup because I thought you might wanna read it.
Aren't I considerate? There's an update on your captain too, but you don't care.
What?
Paper! You have to give it to me!
Okay, okay. You're freaking me out.
Hey, are you done yet? My hands are getting tired.
Hold on a sec. There's something going on here.
Normally, Luffy wouldn't do something like this.
Rayleigh's with him, so it must be some idea he cooked up.
There's gotta be a catch here.
I don't care. Just hurry it up, will ya?
GAUGHT!
wu-yeah!
ahh...!
Towards that later, Luffy's crew
Gah!
Dammit.
Luffy's crew receives his message.
Meanwhile, a battle to become one of the four emperors
breaks out among pirates now in the New World.
As the fighting intensifies,
a Navy Admiral appears to wipe out the pirates.
On the next One Piece,
pirates get on the move!
Astounding New World!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!